<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: quotes | Techno]]></title>
  <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/categories/quotes/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-07-03T18:10:24+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Sachin Patil]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is addictive, I'm hooked! Linux Quotes Collection]]></title>
    <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2009/08/30/linux-is-addictive-im-hooked-linux/"/>
    <updated>2009-08-30T10:32:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2009/08/30/linux-is-addictive-im-hooked-linux</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
After a big break, Today, <br /><br />I will be presenting collection of Linux related quotes,<br /><br />1) In most countries selling harmful things like drugs is punishable.<br />Then howcome people can sell Microsoft software and go unpunished? (By hasku@rost.abo.fi, Hasse Skrifvars).<br /><br />2) This message was brought to you by Linux, the free unix.<br />Windows without the X is like making love without a partner.<br />Sex, Drugs & Linux Rules<br />win-nt from the people who invented edlin<br />apples have meant trouble since eden<br />Linux, the way to get rid of boot viruses<br />(By mwikholm@at8.abo.fi, MaDsen Wikholm).<br /><br />3) Avoid the Gates of Hell. Use Linux<br />(Unknown source)<br /><br />4)  linux: because a PC is a terrible thing to waste(ks @cis.ufl.edu put this on Tshirts in '93)<br /><br />5) `When you say "I wrote a program that crashed Windows", people just stare at<br />you blankly and say "Hey, I got those with the system, *for free*".'<br />(By Linus Torvalds).<br /><br />6) "World domination. Fast."<br />(By Linus Torvalds)<br /><br />7) "...Unix, MS-DOS, and Windows NT (also known as the Good, the Bad, and<br />the Ugly)."<br />(By Matt Welsh)<br /><br />8) "Linux: the operating system with a CLUE... Command Line User Environment".<br />(seen in a posting in comp.software.testing)<br /><br />9)  *** mailing list about a kernel bug ***<br />I'm an idiot.. At least this one [bug] took about 5 minutes to find.."<br />(Linus Torvalds in response to a bug report.)<br />> I'm an idiot.. At least this [bug] took about 5 minutes to find..<br />Disquieting ...<br />(Gonzalo Tornaria in response to Linus Torvalds's mailing about a kernel bug.)<br />> I'm an idiot.. At least this [bug] took about 5 minutes to find..<br />We need to find some new terms to describe the rest of us mere mortals<br />then.<br />(Craig Schlenter in response to Linus Torvalds's mailing about a kernel bug.)<br />> I'm an idiot.. At least this [bug] took about 5 minutes to find..<br />Surely, Linus is talking about the kind of idiocy that others aspire to :-).<br />(Bruce Perens in response to Linus Torvalds's mailing about a kernel bug.)<br />*********************************************************************<br />10)  As usual, this being a 1.3.x release, I haven't even compiled this<br />kernel yet.  So if it works, you should be doubly impressed.<br />(Linus Torvalds, announcing kernel 1.3.3 on the linux-kernel mailing list.)<br />11) it's a bird..<br />It's a plane..<br />No, it's KernelMan, faster than a speeding bullet, to your rescue.<br />Doing new kernel versions in under 5 seconds flat..<br />(Linus, in the announcement for 1.3.27)<br /><br />12) >Linux is not user-friendly.<br />It _is_ user-friendly.  It is not ignorant-friendly and idiot-friendly.<br />(Seen somewhere on the net.)<br /><br />13) "How do you power off this machine?"<br />(Linus, when upgrading linux.cs.helsinki.fi, and after using the machine<br />for several months.)<br /><br />14) Excusing bad programming is a shooting offence, no matter _what_ the<br />circumstances.<br />(Linus Torvalds, to the linux-kernel list)<br />15) If Bill Gates is the Devil then Linus Torvalds must be the Messiah.<br />(Unknown source)<br /><br />16) Vini, vidi, Linux!<br />(Unknown source)</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
