<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: gtk | Techno]]></title>
  <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/categories/gtk/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-08-30T15:15:41-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Sachin Patil]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eclipse Juno : Rememberer previously open file tabs under visible tabs]]></title>
    <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2012/07/31/eclipse-juno-rememberer-previously-open-file-tabs-under-visible-tabs/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-31T14:15:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2012/07/31/eclipse-juno-rememberer-previously-open-file-tabs-under-visible-tabs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you tried Eclipse Juno, you may see strange behaviour with open tabs in editors. Juno has stopped retaining open file tabs tabs. If you open new file using <code>Ctrl Shift R</code>, it closes last active file . This behaviour is started in Juno.</p>

<p>If you take a look in the preferences, in the appearance section, you won’t find anything related to this.</p>

<p>The good news is that I found fix, rather work around :). Go to Preferences -> General -> Appearance and switch to the Classic theme. Yes, switching theme solved this issue.</p>

<p>I am still looking for correct fix, let me know if you find one.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[mouse clicks in Eclipse does not work after Karmic upgrade]]></title>
    <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2009/11/24/mouse-clicks-in-eclipse-does-work-after/"/>
    <updated>2009-11-24T04:33:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2009/11/24/mouse-clicks-in-eclipse-does-work-after</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
After upgrade to Ubuntu Karmic, mouse clicks stopped in <a href="http://www.eclipse.org/">eclipse</a>, my favourite IDE, mainly for submit buttons. Until today I used keyboard as alternative, but it was bit frustrating. <br /><br />  This issue raised because karmic brings version 2.18 of GTK+ to the desktop. GTK+ is a multi-platform toolkit for creating graphical user interfaces. Offering a complete set of widgets, the GTK+ is suitable for projects ranging from small one-off tools to complete application suites.<br /><br />Eclipse assume that they can just operate on the X windows corresponding to their GDK windows without ever telling GDK, which causes some widgets to exhibit weird behaviour. <a href="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/show_bug.cgi?id=287307">Bug 287307</a> was filed with the Eclipse foundation and this is fixed for the upcoming 3.6 release.<br /><br />Fortunately, the GTK+ people provide a switch to turn off the client side windows. So to work around the bug with Eclipse pre-3.6, just make sure you set environment variable GDK_NATIVE_WINDOWS=1  <br /> I created simple eclipse launcher script which will set this variable.<br /><br /><pre name="code" class="cpp"><br />#!/bin/sh<br />export GDK_NATIVE_WINDOWS=1<br />/home/sachin/opt/eclipse3.5/eclipse<br /><br /></pre><br /><br />and added it to /usr/bin.<br /><br />  Happy coding!!!</div>


<h2>Comments</h2>


<div class='comments'>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>Anonymous</div>
<div class='content'>
Thanks Sachin!!!<br />I have been puzzling over this for a long time!!!  With your help, this finally worked!!!<br />Thank you again!</div>
</div>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>Anonymous</div>
<div class='content'>
Thanks a lot. Made my day.<br /><br />Igor</div>
</div>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>Heryy</div>
<div class='content'>
Thanks...<br />Worked for me too.</div>
</div>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
