<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Java | Techno]]></title>
  <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/categories/java/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-07-03T18:08:19+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Sachin Patil]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Java to Python, I'm loving it.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2009/12/15/from-java-to-python-im-loving-it/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-15T21:33:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://sacdroid.github.com/blog/2009/12/15/from-java-to-python-im-loving-it</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Its been just three months, I learnt <a href="http://www.python.org/">Python</a> (or I started learning it as there many more aspects to learn) and  I am already very fond of it. Especially I have started using python for scripting work. I automated few things using python scripts which I had to do regularly like a creating users in oracle, copying / importing oracle dumps, syncing Wiki svn log with svn sever and many more. <br />  Some might argue that you can do the same thing in shell scripts or other programming languages. You can do that  but coding in python is 5-10 times faster and <a href="http://pythonconquerstheuniverse.wordpress.com/category/java-and-python/">this article</a> gives insight comparative of Java with python.<br />  To create connection in Java, it involves three steps but with python its just one step<br /><pre name="code" class="py"><br />    conn = cx_Oracle.connect(username, password, sid)<br /></pre><br />  <br />  I am not bad-mouthing Java here. With <a href="http://java.sun.com/javaee/">JEE6</a> at doorstep, Java has progressed very well as web technologies. <br />  For now, I will be using python for writing utility scripts unless I get chance to work on real big python Project.<br />  As experienced Java programmers, I found this <a href="http://python.computersci.org/">e-book</a> very helpful for learning python <br />  Coding in python as easy as in Java, I have already written <a href="http://cricscoreapplet.sourceforge.net/">cricket live score</a> gnome applet in python which been huge success.<br /><br /> Being interpreted language Python is little bit slow. With the Java just-in-time compiler, Java is faster.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
